Good afternoon, sir.
What is your name?
Unrecognized command.
My name is Dragonfire.
Who am I?
Your name is Mehmet Mert Yıldıran, sir.
What is your gender?
I have a female voice, but I don't have a gender identity. I'm a computer program, sir.
I'm a girl.
Pardon, my lady.
What is your gender?
I have a female voice, but I don't have a gender identity. I'm a computer program, my lady.
I'm a boy.
Pardon, sir.
Dragonfire
Yes, I'm waiting.
Open file manager
File manager
Open web browser
Web browser
Wikipedia search for Oxford University.
Unrecognized command.
(Reading the content...)
Enough!
Dragonfire
Yes, sir.
YouTube search for Oxford University.
Studying at Oxford University
YouTube search for Oxford.
A Day in the Life of an Oxford Student.
[ Thanks for watching! ]